



Fresher ReactJS, Python Web

Nguyen Viet Xuan

To apply my knowledge in the field of Javascript and Python programming into pratical use.

Looking forward to working in a professional environment.

To learn and to improve my professional experiences and other skills particularly of Javascript, backend Nodejs or Python.

What I Do



Web Design

Freelancer Python Django 1 year of experience.

Fresher ReactJS 2 months of practical experience.

Fresher

Resume

Education

2015-2020

University of Information Technology (UIT)

Information Security

Learn about malware analysis, system testing, Vulnerability Analysis, Firewalls, IDS/IPS system, etc.

Experience

JULY 2018 - SEP 2018

Certified Network Security Center (CNSC)

Interns

- Experienced in doing research with lectures
- Experienced in using Django and Flask to write API

JULY 2018 - Now Thai Binh Engineering and Trading

IT Part-time

- Web application development with Django smartthuanviet.cf
- Website management
- It help desk

OCT 2019- DEC 2019 Beesight Soft

Fresher Reactjs

- Co-ordinated with ReactJS in doing projects

Skills

- Programming language: Javascript ,Python, C++, C#.
- Basic knowledge: Object Oriented Programming (OOP), Structured Query Language (SQL), HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Linux, Git.
- Framework: ReactJS, Django, Flask.
- Platform: Nodejs.
- Knowledgedgeable in information security.
- Skilled in teamwork.
- Dynamic in adopting new technology into working.

Get in Touch

Contact



Phone Numbers

0869 123 020 - 0797 07 10 97



Address

Dorm B, Vietnam national university Ho Chi Minh city, Di An, Binh Duong.



Email

vietxuandev@gmail.com



Facebook

fb.com/VietXuanDev



Instagram

instagram.com/vietxuandev





http://vietxuandev.com